Guide to the Papers of Harrison Salisbury,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Box Listing (unsorted)
  - Chinese Sheet Music: Inscribed to Salisbury and CYS from Hsia Yen Chou and Chou Hsia-yen (some inscriptionss in Chinese) (Box 649, Folder 20)
  - Lenin: -- Mostly re Lenin, RFE, etc. (Box 649, Folder 21)
  - Fofanova: For Salisbury pp. re Lenin, (1 Mss., 2 Audiocassettes) (Box 649, Folder 22)
  - Li Bazhao The Long March, Beijing, 1951, (Photocopy, book) (Box 649, Folder 23)
  - Lide Yu, Zhongguo Geming Photocopy, Book (Box 649, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous [In Italian] re Salisbury's The Long March trip -- Recalling the Long March, by Liu Po-cheng and others (Peking, Foreign Languages Press) (Box 649, Folder 25)
  - Lenin Last Period [Some in Russian] (Box 649, Folder 26)
  - Povest' o Ninapsannoi Knige: Photocopied pp. from in Russian, pp. 379-557, (Book ) (Box 649, Folder 27)
  - China and the Long March: Retracing the Steps. Photocopied spiral-bound by Harold Weldon, 1985, (Mss. ) (Box 650, Folder 29)
  - Stories of the Long March: Peking: Foreign Languages Press, 1958, (Photocopy, Book ) (Box 650, Folder 30)
  - On the Long March With Chairman Mao: Edition of Peking: Foreign Languages Press, 1972, (Photocopy, Book ) (Box 650, Folder 31)
  - On the Long March with Chairman Mao: Edition of Peking: Foreign Languages Press, 1959, (Photocopy, Book ) (Box 650, Folder 32)
  - Liu Po-cheng Recalling the Long March: Peking: Foreign Languages Press, 1978, (Photocopy, Book ) (Box 650, Folder 33)
  - R. A. Bosshardt The Restraining Hand: London: Hodder and Stoughton, 1936, (Photocopy, Book ) (Box 650, Folder 34)
  - Maisk. Y Ivan Maisky, 1977 (Box 650, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous: To and from Salisbury. (Box 650, Folder 36)
  - Travel: London Trip: To and from Salisbury. 27 July - 20 August 1978, (Theater Programs, Receipts, Notes, Promo & Business Letters ) (Box 650, Folder 38)
  - CYS, 1991-1993, (Letters, Correspondence ) (Box 650, Folder 39)
  - Published Material re. China: -- Chinese-language, at Tienanmen, 1989 -- 1986 journal (in English) -- Mao 1970 (in English) (Box 650, Folder 40)
  - Heroes of My Time, (Reviews ) (Box 650, Folder 41)
  - Newspaper, Journal List, Soviet Publications, etc.: "Given to Columbia U., 6/7/74" written on top -- Ad for Paul Verhoeven film, "Leningrad," based on Salisbury (Box 650, Folder 42)
  - Picture, Letter, Postcards, Souvenirs: Most addressed to Salisbury or various relatives -- To Sue Salisbury 1882 -- Souvenir plate from Birmingham, AL -- Souvenir wood plaque from Vologda, Russia., 1902-1941 (Box 650, Folder 43)
  - Arthur Miller Film Project: Removed from Inge Morath and Arthur Miller, In Russia (NY: Viking, 1969), inscribed to Harrison and Charlotte, The New York Times, (Clipping ) (Box 651, Folder 1)
  - To Moscow And Beyond: Note to Charlotte, in Chinese removed from Chinese translation of Salisbury -- "To Moscow And Beyond", inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison, (Card, Note ) (Box 651, Folder 2)
  - American Heritage Publishing Co.: Note to Salisbury from Samuel Reed,: Removed from Bernard A. Weisberger, Cold War, Cold Peace: The United States and Russia Since 1945 (NY: American Heritage, 1984), with Salisbury introduction, (Note ) (Box 651, Folder 3)
  - Notes: Page of Salisbury removed from Salisbury, eD., The Eloquence of Protest: Voices of the 70's (Boston: Houghton Mifflin, 1972) -- Between pp. 208-209 (Box 651, Folder 4)
  - Letter: To Charlotte, Salisbury notes removed from Jung Chang, Wild Swans: Three Daughters of China (NY: Simon and Schuster, 1991) -- Note written on endpaper, "P. 352 reached by Harrison", probably Charlotte's writing (Box 651, Folder 5)
  - Letters: To Charlotte and Harrison, one to Charlotte from Demi removed from Demi [Hintz], The Magic Boat (NY: Henry Holt & CO., 1990), inscribed to Charlotte and Harrison from Demi (Box 651, Folder 6)
  - Letter: Lettter to Salisbury from C. Lester Stermer, International House of Chicago, removed from: A Search for Solutions: USA - USSR (International House of Chicage, 1984) (Box 651, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Cards: From Sam Vaughan, Doubledayremoved from Elaine Wilson, eD., Images of Christmas (Garden City: Doubleday, 1984) (Box 651, Folder 8)
  - Authors' Note: Removed from Stewart and Ann Hoskins, Christmas Is Always: Prose and: Inscribed to Charlotte and Harrison from authors, (Poetry ) (Box 651, Folder 9)
  - A Time of Change: Salisbury removed from uncorrected proof of Salisbury,(pp. 284-5), (Notes ) (Box 651, Folder 10)
  - Card: Removed from Thomas P. Whitney, eD. and /tranS., The New Writing in Russia (Ann Arbor: University of Michigan Press, 1964) (Box 651, Folder 11)
  - Memoir, Mss., Notes: Beginning of (pp. 330-1) -- Post-it (P. 501) removed from James Michener, The World is My Home: A (NY: Random House, 1992) -- Advance uncorrected proof (Box 651, Folder 12)
  - American Committee on the History of the Second World War: Removed from William Woodruff, Vessel of Sadness (London: Chatto and Windus, 1970), November 1974, (Newsletter ) (Box 651, Folder 13)
  - Kentucky Fair: Mark removed from Mona Simpson, Anywhere But Here (NY: Knopf, 1987), inscribed to Charlotte from author, Nov 19, 1988, (Book ) (Box 651, Folder 14)
  - Publisher's to Salisbury: Removed from Mary E. Mebane, Mary (NY: Vuiking, 1981), dedicated in part to Salisbury, (Letter ) (Box 651, Folder 15)
  - Publisher's to Salisbury: Removed from David Irving, The Destruction of Dresden (NY: Holt, Rhinehart, & Winston, 1963), (Letter, Review, Notes ) (Box 651, Folder 16)
  - Invoice: Removed from G. M. Katkov, Fevral'skaia Revoliutsiia (Paris: YMCA Press, 1984) (Box 651, Folder 17)
  - Note: Removed from Zhores A. Medvedev, 10 Years After Ivan Denisovich (NY: Macmillan, 1973), in Russian (Box 651, Folder 18)
  - Times Literary Supplement: pp. 637-8 removed from Iosif Brodskii (Joseph Brodsky), Stikhotvoreniia i Poemy (Washington: Inter-Language Literary Associates, 1965), Aug 20, 1967 (Box 651, Folder 19)
  - Book, Notes, Reviews: Removed from Salisbury, The Many Americas Shall Be One (NY: W. W. Norton, 1971), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison (papers between pp. 16-17 (Box 651, Folder 20)
  - Review: Removed from Salisbury, To Moscow -- And Beyond (NY: Harper and BroS., 1960), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison -- Papers pp. 130-131, New York Times, 28 March 1960 (Box 651, Folder 21)
  - Reviews: Removed from Salisbury, Moscow Journal (University of Chicago Press, 1961), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison -- Papers pp. 412-413 (Box 651, Folder 22)
  - Minnesota Centennial Show: Removed from Salisbury, American In Russia (NY: Harper and BroS., 1955), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison (1962), paper P. 143, (Postcards ) (Box 651, Folder 23)
  - Book, Review: Removed from Salisbury, A Time of Change (NY: Cornelia and Michael Bessie s, 1988), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison -- Papers pp. 96-97, New York Times, 20 March 1988 (Box 651, Folder 24)
  - Notes: Removed from Salisbury, Black Night, White Snow (Garden City: Doubleday, 1978), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison -- Papers pp. 268-9 (Box 651, Folder 25)
  - Postcards: From Edgartown, Martha's Vineyard. Removed from Salisbury, The New Emperors (Boston: Little, Brown, 1992), pp. 106-7 (Box 651, Folder 26)
  - The New Yorker: Removed from Gordon N. Ray, H. G. Wells and Rebecca West (New Haven: Yale University Press, 1974), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison, (Review ) (Box 651, Folder 27)
  - Publishers' Card: Removed from Davis R. Sharpe, Americans and Russians: Readings with Exercises in Composition (NY: Scribners, 1965), pp. 286-7 (Box 651, Folder 28)
  - Note to Charlotte: Removed from Maria Luisa Scott and Jack Denton Scott, Informal Dinners for Easy Entertaining (NY: Simon and Schuster, 1975), inscribed to Harrison and Charlotte from Jack -- Papers from pp. 178-179 (Box 651, Folder 29)
  - "Note to Harrison and Charlotte": From Beth and Sam (Walker). Removed from Margaret Mead and Rhoda Matraux, An With Santa Claus (NY: Walker and CO., 1978), (Interview ) (Box 651, Folder 30)
  - Postcards: re The Junior Fortnightlyremoved from Arthur Miller, Timebends: A Life (NY: Grove Press, 1987), inscribed to Harrison and Charlotte from Arthur -- Papers from pp. 20-21 (Box 651, Folder 31)
  - Promotional Cocktail Napkin: Removed from Lu Yu, The Classic of Tea (Boston: Little, Brown, 1974), inscribed to Charlotte and Harrison from translator and illustrator -- Papers from pp. 80-81 (Box 651, Folder 32)
  - Business Card, Promotional Material: Removed from Three Short Plays By Anne Paolucci (Whitestone, NY: Gritton House, 1994) (Box 651, Folder 33)
  - Family Shelf: Removed from CYS, Russian Diary (NY: Walker and CO., 1974), inscribed to Harrison from Charlotte, (Brochures, Book ) (Box 651, Folder 34)
  - The The Long March: Removed from Salisbury, The Long March: The Untold Story (NY: Harper and Row, 1985), inscribed to Charlotte from Harrison, (Photo, Magazine ) (Box 651, Folder 35)
  - Salisbury family history index: -- File in Shoeboxes, (Cards ) (Box 652 & 653)
  - Photographs (Box 652 & 653)
  - Photo, List of Subjects, Several Sheets on a Legal Pad (Box 654, Folder 1)
  - [The Great Black Dragon Fire]: Forest Fire: Enlargements, b&w and color, (Snapshots, Captions, Negatives, Photo ) (Box 654, Folder 2)
  - The Long March: Enlargements of Salisbury with Chinese officials -- Some Long March pictures with Salisbury from Chinese Press and Publication Administration, (Color Snapshots, Letter, Photos ) (Box 654, Folder 3)
  - The Long March BookTour: JSS [John S. Service] Color Prints [Long March] 5x7 b&w pictures with, (Color Snapshots, Negatives, Book ) (Box 654, Folder 4)
  - The Long March: Color and b&w, to Salisbury from Modern Maturity, (Snapshots, Letter, Slides ) (Box 654, Folder 5)
  - Color Snapshots, Negatives, Photographs, Slides: Important LM b&w and enlargements (5x7) -- Some new prints of/from actual Long March (some in bags, envelopes) (Box 654, Folder 6)
  - Good China: Some Tienanmen, many in envelopes (some labelled) -- Liu Binyan at Taconic -- Chinese-American Writers Conferences, 1984, 1988 -- Some old LM -- Salisbury Chinese ID, 1984-1989, (Photographs ) (Box 655, Folder 7)
  - Family: On Chinese, Removed from #7-- including Rome and Capri, 1990 -- CYS and Daisy (dog) -- Steff and Jennifer -- Christmas 1989 -- Salisbury and granddaughters, (Photographs) (Box 655, Folder 8)
  - The Long March, (Photos, Slides ) (Box 655, Folder 9)
  - Russian Voznesenskii at Taconic: CYS with Kornei Chukovsky (slides) -- Salisbury and Bella Akhmadulina, (Color Snapshots, Photographs) (Box 655, Folder 10)
  - Family: Christmas 1986 with Janet, Mike, Molly, et aL., Salisbury as sort of Santa -- CYS "dark", (Photographs) (Box 655, Folder 11)
  - Asia: India 1966, Lhasa 1980, Long March, (Photographs) (Box 655, Folder 12)
  - China: b&w in envelopes, a few labelled -- Packet of slides labelled "LM dupes for TV, etc.", (Snapshots, Photographs, Slides ) (Box 656, Folder 13)
  - Photographs and Subject Lists: May go with #13, or with boxes of slides (Box 656, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Framed CYS in Tibetan Dress -- Not in Folders :boxes of slides, most numbered -- may correspond to lists in folder 14 (some boxes labelled) (Box 656, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Service at Century Association: Texts by CYS, Michael, granddaughters, Gwendolyn Brooks, Arthur Schlesinger, 1993, (Invitation, Memorial Service Lists, Lists of Invitees ) (Box 657, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, Publicity, 1971-1993 (Box 657, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous: To Salisbury and to CYS, From Salisburys -- 1993 from China, 1976-1997, (Christmas Cards, Color Snapshots, etc.) (Box 657, Folder 3)
  - Tytell Typewriter Repair Company, 1980-1994 (Box 657, Folder 4)
  - Papers removed from books: 5 Removed from Ruth Adler, eD., The Working Press: Special to The New York TimesÊ(New York: G. P. Putnam's Sons, 1966) -- "Compliments of the Author", (Card ) (Box 657)
  - Removed from The U.S.S.R. in Today's World: The M. L. Seidman Memorial Town Hall Lecture Series (Memphis State University Press, 1969) -- bookmark (Box 657, Folder 6)
  - Press Release, Book: Removed from Essential Liberty: First Amendment Battles for a Free Press (New York: Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism, 1992) -- about the (Box 657, Folder 7)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander Photograph with two freinds: Removed from Essential Liberty: First Amendment Battles for a Free Press (New York: Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism, 1992) -- about the, [n.p.], [n.d.], (1 photograph ) (Box 658, Folder 11)
  - Times Talk Obituary of Harrison Salisbury: Removed from Essential Liberty: First Amendment Battles for a Free Press (New York: Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism, 1992) -- about the, New York Times, 1993, (1 page Obituary ) (Box 658, Folder 12)
  - Address book &amp -- names cards, (1 folder, ca. 200 items) (Box 658, Folder 13)
  - Mss., Op-ed: Apparently only those selected for publication, The New York Times, 1970 (Box 663, Folder 22-33)
  - National Book Committee, 1972, 1973, 1974 (Box 666)
  - Miscellaneous Salisbury material: Includes one Posthumous folder, 1969-1990, (Correspondence, Christmans Cards, Invitations, Programs, Publicity, Clippings, Op-Ed, Photos ) (Box 667, Folder 5 - 14)
  - Travel: Embassy of the US and Royal Ministry for Foreign Affairs. Includes pictures of Mongolia, Great Wall and clips before "1964", Stockholm, 1974, (Correspondence, Clips, Photos ) (Box 668, Folder 1 - 4)
  - Daily Reports, Letters, Memos: Includes Rosenthal, Ochs, Reston, AMR-AOS sr., AHS and retirement letters of 09/73, New York Times, 1943-1974 (Box 669, Folder 5, 7, 8, 12, 51)
  - Salisbury Family Correspondence: -- Letters, Cards, Christmas Cards, Magazine and Newspaper Clips: Includes General Correspondence III, 1985 and Unsorted Correspondence I, 1980, 1956-1989 (Box 670)
  - Printed Materials, Reviews: -- "Tribute to Mrs Roosevelt", Wyatt Cooper -- Girboyedov, Ivry, Radashkevich -- "Is It Possible To Live in The USSR", Netchaev -- "Defenses of Peace", Stephen Seadler -- Screenplay, James Stark -- Jim Szili, untitled -- "An Experiment in Barriada Education in Lima", Rosina Warner -- Northern Palmyara Affair reviews -- Tom Whitney -- HES (Box 671)
  - Russia and China, (Correspondence, Notes ) (Box 672)
  - Pictures And Posters: -- Julia Taber -- Robert Taber -- Drawings by PPS -- Map of Headquarters -- Sakharov Homage -- Diploma -- Scenery -- YMCA and Red Cross Citations from War Personnel Board -- Regan in Bedtime for Brezhnev -- Plans -- Map of 14 mile hike, 1921 -- Japanese Art from Teruko Iwaya -- Some Russian posters (Box Flat Box 213)
  - New York Times, 1966-1982, (Correspondence ) (Box 665, Folder 1)
  - Monica Highland 110 Shanghai Road, 17 July 1986, (Notes, Correspondence, Clippings, etc. ) (Box 665, Folder 54)
  - Letters of Gray Francine, 1987-1990, (Letters ) (Box 665, Folder 56)
  - Benjamin A. Franklin: Letters, Notes, Memos, 1962-1989 (Box 665, Folder 57)
  - Fairbank, K. John Letters, Notes, Memos, 1989-1991 (Box 665, Folder 60)
  - Onassis Doubleday &amp -- Company, Inc., New York, 1987, (Proposal, Clippings ) (Box 665, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, Clippings, Notes: Kennedy -- Sakharov, USSR -- Chernobyl -- Hanoi -- China -- Russia (Box 665)
  - Dartmouth Conference XV, Baku, 1986, (Note Book, Proposals, Notes ) (Box 660, Folder 7)
  - Balck Night White Snow, 1978, (Reviews, Newspaper Clippings ) (Box 660, Folder 8)
  - Balck Night White Snow, 1980, (Reviews, Clippings, Letters ) (Box 660, Folder 9)
  - Princeton Class, Spring 1986, (Newspaper Clippings, Letters, Notes, Booklets ) (Box 660, Folder 10)
  - 60th Birthday of Harrison Salisbury, (Greetings, Newspaper Clippings ) (Box 659, Folder 1)
  - In Memoriam: Barbara Wertheim Tuchman, (Programs ) (Box 659, Folder 2)
  - The Book Enchained (Box 659, Folder 3)
  - Krock Arthur Letters, Correspondence, Washington, 1944 (Box 659, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy Letters, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 659, Folder 5)
  - Lectures, January - March 1986, (Letters, Correspondence ) (Box 659, Folder 6)
  - Lectures, April - June 1986, (Letters, Correspondence ) (Box 659, Folder 7)
  - Lectures, July 1986 - October 1986, (Letters, Correspondence ) (Box 659, Folder 8)
  - Lectures, Jan 1991 - Sep 1991, (Clippings, Letters, Notes ) (Box 661, Folder 11)
  - Lectures, Oct 1991 - Dec 1991, (Newspaper Clippings, Letters, Notes ) (Box 661, Folder 12)
  - Receptions &amp -- Meetings, 1991, (Miscellaneous Notes & Letters ) (Box 661, Folder 13)
  - North Vietnam &amp -- Russian Art, (Books ) (Box 661, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook with newpapers clippings Family Register of Caroline Salisbury Prints of paintings and sketches Japanese prints Album with clippings Picture of HES, Arthur Miller, CYS, Olga Carlyle, ( 1 Album, etc.) (Box 214)
  - Mountain Top Kingdom: Sikkim -- 2 Ledgers -- Folder w/ newspaper clippings and photos, (Review, Ledgers ) (Box 215)
  - Books: -- A Cynic's Meditations, Walter Pulitzer -- Notes From the "News", James Payn -- In The Tennessee Mountains, Charles E Craddock -- The Age - A Colloquial Satire, Philip J Bailey -- The Superstar Show of Government, Roger G Schwartzenberg -- Mental Philosophy, Joseph Haven -- Portrait of Birmihgham, Birmingham Centennial Corporation, (7 books ) (Box 673)
  - "Three Cheers for Harry and The OEP!!!": Map Case 14/14/07, The New York Times, Sept 21, 1970 (Box 14/14/07, Folder 1)
  - "Surprising How Much You Can See Through an Iron Curtain": Map Case 14/14/07, The New York Times, Aug 29, 1951 (Box 14/14/07, Folder 1)
  - The Franklin Library Signed First Edition Society: Map Case 14/14/07 -- Awarded to the Creative Writing Program, Princeton University, 1988, (Photgraph, Signatures ) (Box 14/14/07, Folder 2)
  - Photographs by Harrison Salisbury of North Vietnam and others: Map Case 14/14/07 (Box 14/14/07, Folder 3)
  - Harrison Salisbury "Behind Russia's Iron Curtain": Stack 15, Cage 26, on the Table, The New York Times, Sept 19, 1953, (1 Poster ) (Folder 1)
  - Route of Mao's Long March: Stack 15, Cage 26, on the Table, (1 Map ) (Box 15/26, Folder 4)
  - Liz Smith "Salisbury's Epic China Tale": Map Case 14/14/07, New York Newsday, 4 February 1992 (Box 14/14/07, Folder 5)
  - Record - Helen Hall Show No 71: interview with Salisbury To Peking and Beyond Miscellaneous Chinese country photos: Album w/ photos of Nov 14, 1978 birthday party Captions for Pictures and photos, Hanoi Photos in New York Times Envelope: Dinner with Premier Chou En-Lai in Great Hall of the People, Peking -- Dinner for 1980 Nixon Scholar -- Other Salisbury photos -- 2 Sketches, 1969 and 1979 -- Poster of University Art Museum, Berkely, 1980 China Art Propaganda photos -- Russia photos for transparencies, 1967 -- Denise Rene Vous Presente Ses Meilleurs Veux, 1999 -- Miscellaneous photographs Miscellaneous Russian and German photographs, 1917-1919 Poster w/Birthday Greetings by Ann Print of oriental painting Video of Harrison Salisbury Project, standard play, 1:20, produced by USC Journalism/Broadcasting, (Album, etc.) (Box 216)
  - Russia in Revolution: -- Photogrpahs of Leon Trotsky -- Czar Nicholas II -- Vladimir Ilyich Lenin -- Joseph Stalin -- Leon Trotsky -- Nikita Kruschev, etc., (ca. 150 Photographs for Book) (Box 674)
  - Salisbury, Charlotte Memorial Book of Letters and Obituaries, Nov 14, 1908 - July 5, 1993, (1 volune of photocopies) (Box 677)
  - Salisbury M. H. & Stef Letters, Notes, Newspaper Clippings, Birthday Card, Memos (Box 678, Folder 4)
    [Permission Required to See, from May 22, 1997 for 30 years, i.e., up to May 21, 2027]
  - H. E. Salisbury Letters, Correspondence, Memos (Box 678, Folder 5)
  - SPS Stories: Newspaper Clippings (Box 678, Folder 6)
  - Awards from The New York Times, (6 framed awards) (Box 679)
  - Salisbury, Harrison E. Medals and memorabilia -- Photo album - conferring of honorary degree, Assumption College (Box 322)
  - Salisbury, Harrison E. Memorabilia: Two plaques (Box 323)
  - Memorabilia: Awards and certificates -- Honorary degrees -- Ernst Naizvestnyi engraving and Jimmy Carter p.d.s. [See card catalog] -- Pulitzer Prize Memorial from New York Times [Gift of C. Salisbury 01/2008] (Box 324)
  - Neivestnyi, Ernst, 1926- [faces], [n.p.], 1968, (29.5 x 21 cm. engraving, signed) (Box 324)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1926- Certificate appointing Harrison E. Salisbury a member of the Board of Foreign Scholarships -- also signed by Edmund S. Muskie as Secretary of State., Washington, DC, 10 November 1980, (1 page p.d.s.) (Box 324)
  - Honoray Degrees: Awards from Colleges and Universities; Certificates (Box 680)
  - Honoray Degrees & Certificates (Box 681)
  - Plaques (Box 682)
  - Plaques & Medals (Box 683)
  - Plaques & miscellaneous large memorabilia (Box 684)
  - Columbia University Certificate awarding Harrison E. Salisbury a Pulitzer Prize in journalism for distinguished reporting of international affairs, New York, 2 May 1955, (1 page p.d.s., 2 copies) (Box 193)
  - Tinkham, Charles B. "For Harrison Salisbury (in appreciation of his book Black Night, White Snow)", [n.p.], [n.d.], (1 page poem) (Box 146)
  - Columbia University Citation for a Pulitzer Prize in journalism for international reporting, New York, 2 May 1955, (1 page p.d.s. (with copy)) (Box 193)
  - New York Times WQXR election coverage, New York, 6 Nov. 1968 (Box 544)
  - Posters: 1. Hunter S. Thompson "Sheriff" 2. J. Brodsky "A Stop in the Desert" [poem] 3. "The Commune's Fish Pond" 4. "17th International Desing Conference" Aspen 5. Neil Welliver "The Birches" Met. Museum of Art (Box 4)
  - 1. Portrait of Katy Davies 2. Painting by Leo A. Hemkore 3. Painting by Harrison Slaisbury 4. Five reproduaction of cowboys hunting (Box 14/16/02, Folder 1 [of 3])
  - 1. Headline of JFK' s assassination 2. Print of a woman's head 3. Cartoon of soldier in trench [humorous] 4. Nine large landscape phorographs of China (Box 14/16/02, Folder 2 [of 3])
  - 1. Poster of Hitler [humorous] 2. Poster of Garibaldi 3. Poster of cartoon "Suarez '83" (Box 14/16/02, Folder 3 [of 3])
  - Posters, various. (Box 18)
    [Added by C. Salisbury 6/2008]
  - The Lakeville Journal "Arthur Miller Remembers His Friend, Harrison Salisbury", 18 April 1996 (Box Box 69)